popularbookmarking.com 2013-12-02

# Privacy | Popular BookMarking

Popularbookmarking.com Privacy Policy

Popularbookmarking knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Popularbookmarking.com, Inc. (“we” or “us”) on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on http://www.Popularbookmarking.com, the Popularbookmarking Reader, and the related services, features, content or applications we offer (collectively, “Popularbookmarking”). In connection with your use of Popularbookmarking, we receive information about you from various sources, including: (i) through your Popularbookmarking user account (your “Account”); (ii) your use of Popularbookmarking generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use Popularbookmarking, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, transmission, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) we gather when you are using or accessing Popularbookmarking. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, content sources, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through Popularbookmarking, or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

**What Information Is Collected by Popularbookmarking?**

The information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and continue to operate Popularbookmarking. In connection with certain aspects of Popularbookmarking, we may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information. We collect the following types of information from our users.

_Sign-In Information:_

When you create an Account or login using your Twitter, Facebook, and/or Google credentials, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your username, password and email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an account with Popularbookmarking and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore may not be anonymous. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services, including without limitation, notifications regarding the Services and, upon your request, email digests of content shared by those that you follow on Popularbookmarking, Twitter, Facebook, and/or Google. You may unsubscribe from these messages through your Account settings, although we regardless reserve the right to contact you when we believe it is necessary, such as for account recovery purposes.

_User Content and URL Information:_

Popularbookmarking allows you to provide content to Popularbookmarking, such as the ability to Popularbookmarking and Submit collections of content and uniform resource locators (“URLs”), written descriptions of content or URLs, comments, text, images and video. We may also collect and store information regarding the content in your Popularbookmarking, Twitter, Facebook, and /or Google feeds and the original URL, and associate that information with your Account. We also collect and store (i) the time and date on which the content was first dugg, submitted, or shared and (ii) information on the channels through which the content was shared, e.g., to other Popularbookmarking users, Twitter followers, Facebook friends, and/or Google connections.

We share certain information about you, such as your username, any avatar or image you elect to post, your Twitter, Facebook, and/or Google username, your reading feeds through Popularbookmarking, Twitter, Facebook, Google, and other Third Party Services, and other information you elect to make public to your followers in Popularbookmarking, your followers on Twitter, your friends on Facebook, and/or your connections on Google. This may include Personal Information, but only to the extent that you decide to share such information with others.

We may retain content submitted by you to Popularbookmarking indefinitely, even after you terminate your Account.

_Popularbookmarking Reader Information:_

If you are a Popularbookmarking Reader user, we will maintain information about the sources and subscriptions, including RSS and other content feeds, that you choose to follow. We will collect and store (i) all articles and posts that are part of your subscribed feeds, (ii) data associated with those items, such as the time and date they were published, (iii) whether and when you viewed, saved, or marked them as read, (iv) information related to your organizational choices, such as the folders or tags you assign to sources, and (v) information necessary to complete actions you may choose to take with particular items, such as Popularbookmarkinging, saving, liking, recommending, or sharing to Third Party Services. If

_Metrics and Analytics:_

We collect information about accesses of content curated through Popularbookmarking, as well as interactions with Popularbookmarking Reader. This information includes, but is not limited to: (i) the IP address and physical location of the devices accessing the curated content or interacting with Popularbookmarking Reader; (ii) the time and date of each access or interactions; and (iii) information about sharing of curated content or content appearing in Popularbookmarking Reader.

_Information Collected From Third Party Services:_

Some features of Popularbookmarking allow you to share your Popularbookmarking curated content and Popularbookmarking Reader content through Third Party Services, as well as your content from Third Party Services through Popularbookmarking. If you choose to connect Popularbookmarking to such Third Party Services, we may collect information related to your use of those Third Party Services, such as authentication tokens that allow us to connect to your Third Party Service accounts. We may otherwise collect information about how you are using Popularbookmarking to interact with those connected Third Party Services. Note that Third Party Services may have the ability to restrict the information that is provided to us.
